I have my white rice here I cooked from the night before.
Delicious fluffy white rice.
This is what we traditionally put our picadillo with.
The white rice and picadillo go hand in hand; they go together.
You place it on the plate.
Well actually, you can also put on the side like in Spanish restaurants.
They'll put the rice in here and picadillo here.
I'm going to do it this way.
I'm going to go ahead and put the rice here.
If you don't want to eat the white rice because it's a little bit unhealthy for you, you can do brown rice.
My mom in her old age is having this whole thing about no white rice.
She's very Cuban and she makes a delicious brown rice, and she goes ahead and puts the picadillo over it.